University of Connecticut 1998.0189
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series IV:, 1986
  - University Files (Red Files)
    - Business Administration, School of: Long Range Facility Plan (Box 11:, Folder 409-410)
    - C (Box 11:, Folder 411)
    - Cabinet Meetings (Box 11:, Folder 412)
    - Center for Instructional Media (Box 11:, Folder 413)
    - Center for Intercultural Communications (Box 11:, Folder 414)
    - Child Development (Box 11:, Folder 415)
    - Collective Bargaining: AAUP (Box 11:, Folder 416)
    - Collective Bargaining: CEO/NF Glasgow (Box 11:, Folder 417)
    - Collective Bargaining: E.O. Smith (Box 11:, Folder 418)
    - Collective Bargaining: UCPEA (Box 11:, Folder 419)
    - Computer Center (Box 11:, Folder 420)
    - Computer Center—Long range plan (Box 11:, Folder 421)
    - Connecticut Technology Advisory Committee (Box 11:, Folder 422-424)
    - Consultants: Peat Marwick Mitchell (Box 11:, Folder 425)
    - Consultants: Cambridge Associates (Box 11:, Folder 426)
    - Consulting Policies (Box 11:, Folder 427)
    - Convocation/Commencement (Box 11:, Folder 428)
    - Convocation (September 3) (Box 11:, Folder 429)
    - Co-op (Box 11:, Folder 430)
    - Cooperative Extension (Box 11:, Folder 431)
    - Development Office (Box 11:, Folder 432-433)
    - Development
      - B (Box 11:, Folder 434)
      - C (Box 11:, Folder 435)
      - Electric Boat (Box 11:, Folder 436)
      - F (Box 11:, Folder 437)
      - GTE (Box 11:, Folder 438)
      - H (Box 11:, Folder 439)
      - M (Box 11:, Folder 440)
      - R-Z (Box 11:, Folder 441)
    - Donations (Box 11:, Folder 442)
    - Dramatic Arts (Box 11:, Folder 443)
    - Ecology: Evolutionary Biology (Box 11:, Folder 444)
    - Economics: Fred Carstensen (Box 11:, Folder 445)
    - Economics Department (Box 11:, Folder 446)
    - Education, School of (Box 11:, Folder 447)
    - Education, School of: Dean Search (Box 11:, Folder 448)
    - Education, School of: Goodkind (Box 11:, Folder 449)
    - Emergency Prep Plan (Box 11:, Folder 450)
    - Emeritus Faculty (Box 11:, Folder 451)
    - Endowed Chairs (Box 11:, Folder 452)
    - Engineering, School of (Box 11:, Folder 453-455)
    - Engineering, School of: Accreditation (Box 11:, Folder 456)
    - English Department (Box 11:, Folder 457)
    - Enrollment (Box 11:, Folder 458)
    - Exchange Programs (Box 12:, Folder 459-470)
    - Extended and Continuing Education (Box 12:, Folder 471)
    - Facilities (Box 12:, Folder 472-473)
    - Faculty Staff Development (Box 12:, Folder 474)
    - Family Studies, School of (Box 12:, Folder 475)
    - Finance and Administration (Box 12:, Folder 476-477)
    - Finance and Administration: Financial Aid (Box 12:, Folder 478)
    - Fine Arts, School of (Box 12:, Folder 479)
    - Foreign Languages Department (Box 12:, Folder 480)
    - Foreign TA Intelligibility Problems (Box 12:, Folder 481)
    - Fraternities and Sororities (Box 12:, Folder 482)
    - Gant, Ed and Margaret (Box 12:, Folder 483)
    - Gehrung Associates (Box 12:, Folder 484)
    - Goals and Objectives (Box 12:, Folder 485)
    - Government Relations (Box 12:, Folder 486-487)
    - Graduate Assistant: Rick Perko (Box 12:, Folder 488)
    - Graduate School (Box 12:, Folder 489)
    - Graduate School: Fred Burke, Travel (Box 12:, Folder 490)
    - Graduate School: Graduate Assistant Stipends (Box 12:, Folder 491)
    - Haskins Laboratories (Box 12:, Folder 492)
    - Hazardous Waste Treatment Lab (Box 12:, Folder 493)
    - Health Center (Box 12:, Folder 494-497)
      - Collective Bargaining (Box 12:, Folder 498)
      - Department of Surgery, Peter Deckers (Box 12:, Folder 499-500)
      - John Dempsey Reorganization Meeting (November) (Box 12:, Folder 501-502)
      - Oral History (Box 12:, Folder 503)
      - Physician of Health Services (Box 12:, Folder 504)
      - Uncas on Thames (Box 12:, Folder 505)
    - Hellenic Studies (Box 12:, Folder 506)
    - Hispanic Concerns (Box 12:, Folder 507)
    - History Department (Box 12:, Folder 508)
    - Historian, State (Box 12:, Folder 509)
    - Hunting Lodge Road Water Line (Box 12:, Folder 510)
    - Institute of Material Sciences (Box 12:, Folder 511)
    - Institute of Public Services (Box 12:, Folder 512)
    - Institutional Relations (Box 12:, Folder 513)
    - Institutional Relations: Davidoff and Partners (Box 12:, Folder 514)
    - Institutional Research (Box 12:, Folder 515-516)
    - International Programs (Box 12:, Folder 517)
    - K (Box 13:, Folder 518)
    - Latin American Studies, Center for (Box 13:, Folder 519)
    - Latin Americans in Higher Education (Box 13:, Folder 520)
    - Law School (Box 13:, Folder 521-525)
    - Liberal Arts and Sciences, College of (Box 13:, Folder 526-527)
    - Meeting (November 25) (Box 13:, Folder 528)
    - Library, Homer Babbidge (Box 13:, Folder 529)
    - M (Box 13:, Folder 530)
    - Mansfield, Town of (Box 13:, Folder 531)
    - Mail, University (Box 13:, Folder 532)
    - Marine Sciences, 1985, 1986 (Box 13:, Folder 533)
    - Medicine, School of (Box 13:, Folder 534)
    - Merit Increases (Box 13:, Folder 535)
    - Minorities (Box 13:, Folder 536)
    - Minorities: CAP Student (Box 13:, Folder 537)
    - Mission Statements (Box 13:, Folder 538)
    - Museum of Art, William Benton (Box 13:, Folder 539)
    - Museum of Natural History (Box 13:, Folder 540)
    - Music Department (Box 13:, Folder 541)
    - Northwood Apartments (Box 13:, Folder 542)
    - Nursing, School of (Box 13:, Folder 543)
    - Ombudsman (Box 13:, Folder 544)
    - Organizational Charts (Box 13:, Folder 545)
    - P (Box 13:, Folder 546)
    - Parents Network (Box 13:, Folder 547)
    - Parking (Box 13:, Folder 548)
    - Personnel (Box 13:, Folder 549)
    - Personnel departures, Vice Presidential Reports (Box 13:, Folder 550)
    - Pharmacy (Box 13:, Folder 551)
    - Philosophy Department (Box 13:, Folder 552)
    - Physical Therapy (Box 13:, Folder 553)
    - Physics Department (Box 13:, Folder 554)
    - Photo Lab (Box 13:, Folder 555)
    - Policy Statement (Box 13:, Folder 556)
    - Political Science Department (Box 13:, Folder 557)
    - President's Driver (Box 13:, Folder 558)
    - President's Internship (Box 13:, Folder 559)
    - President's Office Staff (Box 13:, Folder 560)
    - Psychology Department, 1985-1986 (Box 13:, Folder 561)
    - Puerto Rican Concerns (Box 13:, Folder 562)
    - Regional Campuses (Box 13:, Folder 563-572)
    - Reorganization (Box 13:, Folder 573-575)
    - Research Foundation/Council (Box 13:, Folder 576)
    - Roper Center (Box 13a:, Folder 577)
    - ROTC (Box 13a:, Folder 578-579)
    - Salaries (Box 13a:, Folder 580)
    - Scholarship (Box 13a:, Folder 581)
    - Scholarship: Gant (Box 13a:, Folder 582)
    - Scholarship: South Africa (Box 13a:, Folder 583)
    - Searches (Box 13a:, Folder 584)
    - Searches: Academic Affairs (Box 13a:, Folder 585)
    - Searches: Administration (Box 13a:, Folder 586)
    - Searches: Finance (Box 13a:, Folder 587)
    - Senate (Box 13a:, Folder 588)
    - Sexual Harassment (Box 13a:, Folder 589)
    - E.O. Smith High School (Box 13a:, Folder 590)
    - Social Inquiry, Institute of (Box 14:, Folder 591)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 14:, Folder 592-594)
    - Sociology (Box 14:, Folder 595)
    - Space Allocation: Gulley Hall (Box 14:, Folder 596)
    - Special Olympics Proposal (Box 14:, Folder 597)
    - Speech/Hearing (Box 14:, Folder 598)
    - Student Affairs and Services (Box 14:, Folder 599-600)
      - Activities Office (Box 14:, Folder 601)
      - Associated Student Commissaries (Box 14:, Folder 602)
      - Counseling and Testing Center (Box 14:, Folder 603)
      - Day of Pride (Box 14:, Folder 604)
      - Food Services (Box 14:, Folder 605)
      - Health Services (Box 14:, Folder 606)
      - Orientation (Box 14:, Folder 607)
      - Student Problems (Box 14:, Folder 608)
    - Student Discipline (Box 14:, Folder 609)
    - Student Discipline: Earl Kelley (Box 14:, Folder 610)
    - Student Organizations
      - Block and Bridle Club (Box 14:, Folder 612)
      - Daily Campus (Box 14:, Folder 613)
      - Intra-Fraternal Council (Box 14:, Folder 614)
      - Nutmeg (Box 14:, Folder 615)
      - Student Union Board of Governors (Box 14:, Folder 616)
      - Undergraduate Student Government (Box 14:, Folder 617)
      - WHUS (Box 14:, Folder 618-619)
    - Disabled Student Services Center (Box 14:, Folder 620)
    - Suggestions (Box 14:, Folder 621)
    - T (Box 14:, Folder 622)
    - Task Force on Program Development at Stamford - Final Report (Box 14:, Folder 623)
    - Technology Center (Box 14:, Folder 624)
    - Telephone Services (Box 14:, Folder 625)
    - Tranportation Department (Box 14:, Folder 626)
    - UCEPI (Box 14:, Folder 627-632)
    - UConn Foundation: Peat Marwick Study (Box 14:, Folder 633)
    - University Professor (Box 14:, Folder 634)
    - University Relations (Box 14:, Folder 635)
    - University Relations Organization Charts (Box 14:, Folder 636-637)
    - (Box 14:, Folder 638)
    - Wilbur Cross: Environmental Study (Box 14:, Folder 639)
    - Women's Center (Box 14:, Folder 640)
    - Women's Studies Program (Box 14:, Folder 641)
  - State Government (Blue Files)
    - Administration Services (Box 14:, Folder 642)
    - Agriculture (Box 14:, Folder 643)
    - Appropriations (Box 14:, Folder 644)
    - Attorney General (Box 14:, Folder 645)
    - Auditor
      - Associated Student Government (Box 14:, Folder 646-648)
      - Cash Management/Prompt Deposits (Box 14:, Folder 649)
      - Exit Interview (June 30) (Box 14:, Folder 650)
      - Fiscal Years Ended June 30, 1984 and 1985 (Box 14:, Folder 651)
      - Gifts, Grants, Donations (Box 14:, Folder 652)
      - Graduate Student Council Activity Fund, 1984-1986 (Box 14:, Folder 653)
      - Greater Hartford Campus Student Activity Fund (Box 14:, Folder 654)
      - Health Center (Box 14:, Folder 655)
      - Institute of Social Inquiry - Roper Center (Box 14:, Folder 656)
      - Internal Auditor (Box 14:, Folder 657)
      - Jorgensen Auditorium Box Office Receipts (Box 14:, Folder 658)
      - Misuse of Funds - Study Abroad, France and Soviet Union (Box 14:, Folder 659)
      - School of Law (Box 14:, Folder 660)
      - School of Social Work (Box 14:, Folder 661)
      - Stamford Branch (Box 14:, Folder 662)
      - Student Lounge/Food Activity Fund (Box 14:, Folder 663)
      - Student Organization Fund, 1984-1986 (Box 14:, Folder 664)
      - UConn Foundation (Box 14:, Folder 665)
    - Commission on Human Rights and Opportunities (Box 15:, Folder 666)
    - Comptroller (Box 15:, Folder 667)
    - Computer Center (Box 15:, Folder 668)
    - Connecticut Council for Higher Education (Box 15:, Folder 669)
    - Connecticut Conference of Independent Colleges (Box 15:, Folder 670)
    - Connecticut State University (Box 15:, Folder 671-672)
    - Department of Consumer Protection (Box 15:, Folder 673)
    - DHE: December (Box 15:, Folder 674-676)
    - DHE: November (Box 15:, Folder 677)
    - DHE: October (Box 15:, Folder 678-679)
    - DHE: September (Box 15:, Folder 680-681)
    - DHE: August (Box 15:, Folder 682)
    - DHE: July (Box 15:, Folder 683-684)
    - DHE: June (Box 15:, Folder 685-686)
    - DHE: May (Box 15:, Folder 687-688)
    - DHE: April (Box 15:, Folder 689-690)
    - DHE: March (Box 15:, Folder 691-692)
    - DHE: February (Box 15:, Folder 693)
    - DHE: January (Box 15:, Folder 694)
    - DHE
      - Administrative Flexibility (Box 15:, Folder 695)
      - Budget (Box 15:, Folder 696)
      - Contracting with Independent Colleges (Box 15:, Folder 697)
      - Education Cost/Equity Extension Funds for Exc 41 (Box 15:, Folder 698-699)
      - Financial Assistance, General Fee (Box 15:, Folder 700)
      - Formula Budgeting Advisory Committee (Box 15:, Folder 701)
      - Higher Education Legislation (Box 16:, Folder 702)
      - Management Information System (Box 16:, Folder 703)
      - Minority Staff Development/Recruitment (Box 16:, Folder 704)
      - Minority Student Access and Retention (Box 16:, Folder 705)
      - Mission Statements (Box 16:, Folder 706)
      - Off-Campus Offerings (Box 16:, Folder 707)
      - Strategic Plan Task Force (Box 16:, Folder 708-711)
      - Tuition Policy (Box 16:, Folder 712)
    - E (Box 17:, Folder 713)
    - Economics, Department of (Box 17:, Folder 714)
    - Education, Department of (Box 17:, Folder 715)
    - Environmental Protection, Department of (Box 17:, Folder 716)
    - Financial Aid Task Force (Box 17:, Folder 717)
    - General Assembly (Box 17:, Folder 718)
    - Governor (Box 17:, Folder 719)
    - Governor's Technology Advisory Board (Box 17:, Folder 720)
    - Independent Colleges and Universities Task Force (January - May) (Box 17:, Folder 721-723)
    - Legislative Inquiries (Box 17:, Folder 724)
    - Lieutenant Governor (Box 17:, Folder 725)
    - Litchfield County Center for Higher Education (Box 17:, Folder 726)
    - Naugatuck Valley Region Higher Education Center (Box 17:, Folder 727)
    - State Personnel Department (Box 17:, Folder 728)
    - Policy and Management, Office of (Box 17:, Folder 729)
    - Properties Review Board (Box 17:, Folder 730)
    - Public Safety (Box 17:, Folder 731)
    - Purchases, Bureau of (Box 17:, Folder 732)
    - State Police (Box 17:, Folder 733)
    - Thames Valley Technical College (Box 17:, Folder 734)
    - Transportation, Department of (Box 17:, Folder 735)
    - Treasurer, State (Box 17:, Folder 736)
    - Veterans' Services (Box 17:, Folder 737)
  - Federal Government (Green Files)
    - Army (Box 17:, Folder 738)
    - Congressional Inquiries (Box 17:, Folder 739)
    - Department of Education (Box 17:, Folder 740)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (Box 17:, Folder 741)
    - Handicap Section 504 (Box 17:, Folder 742)
    - Department of Labor, Federal Contract Compliance Programs (Box 17:, Folder 743)
    - Military Academy, U.S. (Box 17:, Folder 744)
    - Gramm-Rudman (Box 17:, Folder 745-746)
    - Gramm-Rudman: Government-University-Industry Research Roundtable Conference, Washington, D.C. (February 26-27) (Box 17:, Folder 747-748)
    - Student Financial Assistance (Box 17:, Folder 749)
  - Organizations (Black Files)
    - Aetna Institute for Corporate Education (Box 17:, Folder 750)
    - B (Box 17:, Folder 751)
    - Bridgeport, University of (Box 17:, Folder 752)
    - C (Box 17:, Folder 753)
    - CBIA (Box 17:, Folder 754)
    - Connecticut Conference of Independent Colleges (Box 17:, Folder 755)
    - Consultants (Box 17:, Folder 756)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 17:, Folder 757)
    - Fulbright Alumni Association (Box 17:, Folder 758)
    - Greater Hartford Chamber of Commerce (Box 17:, Folder 759)
    - Gryzb, Ben (Box 17:, Folder 760)
    - H (Box 17:, Folder 761)
    - Hartford, City of (Box 17:, Folder 762)
    - Hartford Courant (Box 17:, Folder 763)
    - J (Box 17:, Folder 764)
    - R. Wood Johnson Foundation (Box 17:, Folder 765)
    - Kellogg Foundation (Box 17:, Folder 766)
    - L (Box 17:, Folder 767)
    - M (Box 17:, Folder 768)
    - N (Box 17:, Folder 769)
    - Peat Marwick (Box 17:, Folder 770)
    - Questionnaires Completed (Box 17:, Folder 771)
    - Reasserting Presidential Control of University Projects (Box 17:, Folder 772)
    - Research Corporation (Box 17:, Folder 773)
    - S (Box 17:, Folder 774)
    - Shell Corporation (Box 17:, Folder 775)
    - T (Box 17:, Folder 776)
    - W (Box 17:, Folder 777)
    - Yale University (Box 17:, Folder 778)
  - Education Associations (Yellow Files)
    - A (Box 17:, Folder 779)
    - ACE (Box 17:, Folder 780)
    - American Physical Therapy Associates (Box 17:, Folder 781)
    - C (Box 17:, Folder 782)
    - Council of Presidents (Box 17:, Folder 783-785)
    - International Research and Exchanges Board (Box 17:, Folder 786)
    - National Education Organizations (Box 17:, Folder 787)
    - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (Box 18:, Folder 788-790)
      - Annual Meeting, Phoenix (November) (Box 18:, Folder 791-792)
      - Committee on Federal Student Financial Assistance (Box 18:, Folder 793)
      - Executive Committee (Box 18:, Folder 794)
      - Federal Legislation Committee (Box 18:, Folder 795)
    - New England Association of Schools and Colleges (Box 18:, Folder 796-797)
    - Organization of Tropical Studies (Box 18:, Folder 798)
- Series V:, 1987
  - University Files (Red Files)
    - Academic Affairs (Box 19:, Folder 799)
    - Accreditation (Box 19:, Folder 800)
    - Accreditation: Property Considerations (Box 19:, Folder 801)
    - Administration: Vice President (Box 19:, Folder 802)
    - Administration: Vice President Speech (Box 19:, Folder 803)
    - Admissions (Box 19:, Folder 804-806)
    - Advertising of University Programs (Box 19:, Folder 807)
    - Aerospace Studies (Box 19:, Folder 808)
    - (Box 19:, Folder 809-820)
    - Afro-American Cultural Center, 1986-1987 (Box 19:, Folder 821)
      - Cooperative Extension Budget Cuts (Box 19:, Folder 822)
      - Cooperative Long Range Planning (Box 19:, Folder 823-824)
      - Dean Search, 1987-1988 (Box 19:, Folder 825)
      - Food Marketing Center, 1987-1988 (Box 19:, Folder 826)
      - Holcomb Farm, Granby (Box 19:, Folder 827)
      - Pathology Building (Box 19:, Folder 828)
      - Task Force (Box 19:, Folder 829-831)
    - Agriculture and Natural Resources (Box 19:, Folder 832)
    - AIDS (Box 19:, Folder 833)
    - Albert E. Moss Wildflower/Wildlife Sanctuary (Box 19:, Folder 834)
    - Alcohol/Drugs (Box 19:, Folder 835-836)
    - Allied Health: Physical Therapy Accreditation (Box 19:, Folder 837)
    - Alternate Retirement/Social Security (Box 19:, Folder 838)
    - Alumni, President's Letters to (Box 19:, Folder 839-840)
    - Alumni Association (Box 19:, Folder 841-843)
    - Alumni Association: Annual Fund (Box 19:, Folder 844)
    - Alumni Association: Faculty Excellence Awards (Box 19:, Folder 845)
    - Alumni Association: Representation Allowance (Box 19:, Folder 846)
    - Alumni House (Box 19:, Folder 847)
    - Archives Building (Box 19:, Folder 848)
    - Assistant to the President: Sandra Harris (Box 19:, Folder 849)
    - Athletics (Box 19:, Folder 850-852)
      - Basketball (Box 19:, Folder 853)
      - Big East (Box 19:, Folder 854)
      - CPIA (Box 19:, Folder 855)
      - Center for Study of Sport in Society (Box 19:, Folder 856)
      - Drug Testing (Box 19:, Folder 857)
      - Fifth Year Scholarship (Box 19:, Folder 858)
      - Gymnastics cancellation (Box 20:, Folder 859)
      - Medicine (Box 20:, Folder 860)
      - NCAA (Box 20:, Folder 861-863)
      - Ski Team Funding (Box 20:, Folder 864)
      - Sports Center, 1985-1987 (Box 20:, Folder 865-869)
      - Student Recruitment by President (Box 20:, Folder 870)
      - UConn Club (Box 20:, Folder 871)
      - Yankee Conference (Box 20:, Folder 872)
    - Attorney (Box 20:, Folder 873)
    - Audit Subcommittee (Box 20:, Folder 874)
    - Auditorium (Box 20:, Folder 875)
    - Auditor (Box 20:, Folder 876-877)
      - Bursar (Box 20:, Folder 878)
      - Daily Campus (Box 20:, Folder 879)
      - Facilities: labor time (Box 20:, Folder 880)
      - Guidelines: use of overhead recoveries, Research Foundation (Box 20:, Folder 881)
      - Internal Audit Search (Box 20:, Folder 882)
      - Regional Campus Cafeterias (Box 20:, Folder 883)
      - Stamford, Student Fee Collection Fraud (Box 20:, Folder 884)
      - Student Employment (Box 20:, Folder 885)
      - Summer Sports Camps, 1986-1988 (Box 20:, Folder 886)
      - Transportation: Improper Meal Reimbursement (Box 20:, Folder 887)
      - Update, 1984-1985 (Box 20:, Folder 888)
    - Barney House (Box 20:, Folder 889)
    - Biobehavioral Science (Box 20:, Folder 890)
    - Biology (Box 20:, Folder 891)
    - Biotechnology (Box 20:, Folder 892)
    - Black Employee Association (Box 20:, Folder 893)
    - Bloodmobile (Box 20:, Folder 894)
    - Board of Trustees (Box 20:, Folder 895)
    - Bomb Threats (Box 20:, Folder 896)
    - Budget, 1987-1988 (Box 20:, Folder 897-898)
    - Budget: Capital Hearings (Box 20:, Folder 899)
    - Budget, 1988-1989: January - June, 1987 (Box 20:, Folder 900-901)
    - Budget, 1988-1989: July - December, 1987 (Box 20:, Folder 902-904)
      - Capital Hearing, August 28 (Box 20:, Folder 905)
    - Budget, 1986-87: vacancy count/money shortfall (Box 20:, Folder 906)
    - Budget: Vice President, Contingency Fund (Box 20:, Folder 907)
    - Bursar (Box 20:, Folder 908)
    - Business, School of (Box 20:, Folder 909)
    - Business Administration, School of
      - Dean Search, 1987-1988 (Box 20:, Folder 910)
      - Facilities Master Plan (Box 20:, Folder 911)
    - By-Laws (Box 21:, Folder 912)
    - Cabinet Retreat, September 18 (Box 21:, Folder 913)
    - CADRI (Box 21:, Folder 914)
    - Catalogs, UConn (Box 21:, Folder 915)
    - Center for Instructional Media (Box 21:, Folder 916)
    - Center for Real Estate and Urban Economic Studies (Box 21:, Folder 917)
    - Center for Visiting Scholars (Box 21:, Folder 918)
    - Chemistry (Box 21:, Folder 919)
    - Child Development Lab (Box 21:, Folder 920)
    - Collective Bargaining
      - AAUP (Box 21:, Folder 921)
      - Classified (Box 21:, Folder 922)
      - Independent (Box 21:, Folder 923)
      - Health Center (Box 21:, Folder 924)
      - UCPEA (Box 21:, Folder 925)
    - Committees (Box 21:, Folder 926)
    - Communications Sciences (Box 21:, Folder 927)
    - Computer Center (Box 21:, Folder 928)
    - ConnTech (Box 21:, Folder 929-930)
    - Consultants, Outside
      - Barton Gillet (Box 21:, Folder 931)
      - A.D. Little (Box 21:, Folder 932)
      - V. Scottron (Box 21:, Folder 933)
    - Convocation (Box 21:, Folder 934)
    - Cooperative Education (Box 21:, Folder 935)
    - Deans' Council (Box 21:, Folder 936)
    - Dental Medicine (Box 21:, Folder 937)
    - Development (Box 21:, Folder 938-939)
      - Annual Fund (Box 21:, Folder 940)
      - Arkava (Box 21:, Folder 941)
      - B (Box 21:, Folder 942)
      - Black Rock Forest (Box 21:, Folder 943)
      - Chase, David (Box 21:, Folder 944)
      - Cooper, Elaine (Box 21:, Folder 945)
      - Culpepper Foundation (Box 21:, Folder 946)
      - Dinners (Charitable Fundraisers) (Box 21:, Folder 947)
      - DuPont de Nemours (Box 21:, Folder 948)
      - Electric Boat (Box 21:, Folder 949)
      - G (Box 21:, Folder 950)
      - H. Gampel (Box 21:, Folder 951)
      - General Electric (Box 21:, Folder 952)
      - Hartford Bishops (Box 21:, Folder 953)
      - Hartford Foundation for Public Giving (Box 21:, Folder 954-955)
      - Howard Hughes Foundation (Box 21:, Folder 956)
      - IBM (Box 21:, Folder 957)
      - Katzenstein (Box 21:, Folder 958)
      - Kellogg (Box 21:, Folder 959)
      - Konover (Box 21:, Folder 960)
      - Kresge (Box 21:, Folder 961)
      - L (Box 21:, Folder 962)
      - Noether Chair In Modern Italian History (Box 21:, Folder 963)
      - Perkin-Elmer Corporation (Box 21:, Folder 964)
      - Putzel, Max (Box 21:, Folder 965)
      - Science Museum (Box 21:, Folder 966)
      - Spakowski (Box 21:, Folder 967)
      - Squires and Steinberg Fund (Box 21:, Folder 968)
      - United Technologies (Box 21:, Folder 969)
      - Van Dusen (Box 21:, Folder 970)
      - Wolff, Thomas (Box 21:, Folder 971)
      - Zwick, Charles (Box 21:, Folder 972)
    - Eastern States Exposition (Box 21:, Folder 973)
    - Economics: Fred Carstensen (Box 21:, Folder 974)
    - Education: Goodkind (Box 21:, Folder 975)
    - Education, School of
      - Dean Search, 1986-1987 (Box 21:, Folder 976)
    - Emeritus Faculty (Box 22:, Folder 977)
    - Endowed Chairs (Box 22:, Folder 978)
    - Engineering (Box 22:, Folder 979)
    - Engineering: Accreditation (Box 22:, Folder 980)